{"test_questions": [[{"question": "DIVA:OPERA", "opta": "producer:theatre", "optb": "director:drama", "optc": "conductor:bus", "optd": "thespian:play", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GRAIN:SALT", "opta": "shard:pottery", "optb": "shred:wood", "optc": "blades:grass", "optd": "chip:glass", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "THRUST:SPEAR", "opta": "mangle:iron", "optb": "scabbard:sword", "optc": "bow:arrow", "optd": "fence:epee", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PAIN:SEDATIVE", "opta": "comfort:stimulant", "optb": "grief:consolation", "optc": "trance:narcotic", "optd": "ache:extraction", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LIGHT:BLIND", "opta": "speech:dumb", "optb": "language:deaf", "optc": "tongue:sound", "optd": "voice:vibration", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "WAN:COLOUR", "opta": "corpulent:weight", "optb": "insipid:flavour", "optc": "pallid:complexion", "optd": "enigmatic:puzzle", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PORK:PIG", "opta": "rooster:chicken", "optb": "mutton:sheep", "optc": "steer:beef", "optd": "lobster:crustacean", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AFTER:BEFORE", "opta": "first:second", "optb": "present:past", "optc": "contemporary:historic", "optd": "successor:predecessor", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INDIGENT:WEALTHY", "opta": "angry:rich", "optb": "native:affluent", "optc": "gauche:graceful", "optd": "scholarly:erudite", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DISTANCE:MILE", "opta": "liquid:litre", "optb": "bushel:corn", "optc": "weight:scale", "optd": "fame:television", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TEN:DECIMAL", "opta": "seven:septet", "optb": "four:quartet", "optc": "two:binary", "optd": "five:quince", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MUNDANE:SPIRITUAL", "opta": "common:ghostly", "optb": "worldly:unworldly", "optc": "routine:novel", "optd": "secular:clerical", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ARMY:LOGISTICS", "opta": "business:strategy", "optb": "soldier:students", "optc": "war:logic", "optd": "team:individual", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GRAVITY:PULL", "opta": "iron:metal", "optb": "north pole:directions", "optc": "magnetism:attraction", "optd": "dust:desert", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FILTER:WATER", "opta": "curtail:activity", "optb": "expunge:book", "optc": "edit:text", "optd": "censor:play", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HOPE:ASPIRES", "opta": "love:elevates", "optb": "film:flam", "optc": "fib:lie", "optd": "fake:ordinary", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CORPOREAL:SPIRITUAL", "opta": "mesa:plateau", "optb": "moron:savant", "optc": "foreigner:immigrant", "optd": "pedagogue:teacher", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SYMPHONY:COMPOSER", "opta": "Leonardo:music", "optb": "Fresco:painter", "optc": "colours:pallet", "optd": "art:appreciation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}